empiretheatres.com 2013-10-20

# Privacy Policy | Empire Theatres

**PRIVACY POLICY  
EMPIRE THEATRES LIMITED**

Empire Theatres Limited (referred to in this Privacy Policy as the "Company") is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information.  
You should familiarize yourself with this Policy, prior to using this website or supplying personal information to the Company. When you provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of the information listed below for the purposes set out in this Policy.

In this Policy, "personal information" means any information about an identifiable individual, but does not include business contact information including the name, title, business address or business telephone number of an employee of any organization.

The Company collects personal information about our customers, including without limitation Empire Insider and/or Reel Babies members, including without limitation name, address, email address, telephone number, language preference, credit card information, and certain of our customers' preferences and opinions regarding our products and services. Such personal information is gathered as a result of customers' purchases of online tickets, gift cards and other purchases or dealings that customers may have with us.

The Company may use and disclose personal information for the following purposes:

  *  To enable customers to make online purchases of tickets, bookings, gift cards or other offerings. Any credit card specific personal information collected in this process is used and disclosed only for processing transactions, unless customers are informed otherwise and provide consent;

  *  To communicate to customers about information, features and services of our Empire Insider, Reel Babies and other promotions, programs, and services;

  *  To seek customer's participation in customer surveys and polls and to understand and analyze the data collected to develop, enhance, market and/or provide products and services to meet customer preferences;

  *  To enable customers to participate in promotions and contests and to administer such promotions and contests;

  *  To confirm identity if customers request a refund or are dealing with lost and found;

  *  To communicate with customers regarding any concerns or queries they may have or regarding any changes to this Policy;

  *  To communicate with customers regarding promotions, contests, offers, incentives, rewards and other pertinent matters such as products or services available from or through us that may be of interest;

  *  To understand and analyze the interests, needs and preferences of customers;

  *  To develop, enhance, market and provide products and services to customers and potential customers; 

  *  To comply with applicable legislation;

  *  To verify age before entering an age restricted movie;

  *  To report and deal with any accident, theft or incident with which you may have been involved, for insurance and/or legal purposes;

  *  For uses and disclosures as permitted or required by law, including without limitation for the purpose of cooperating with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, and to protect the rights, property or safety of the Company or others;

  *  To provide as part of the Company's customer database to another company or business in the event of a proposed or actual transfer of ownership of all or part of the Company to such other company or business, but for this purpose we shall not authorize any use or disclosure of personal information beyond the scope of the consent that customers  have provided to us;

  *  To our suppliers and contractors who provide services or to us, including without limitation in respect of marketing, the sponsorship or management of  sweepstakes or other  promotions, services or products for our business and in respect of the analysis of data (including without limitation personal information) we have collected. We shall not authorize such suppliers and contractors to use or disclose such information beyond the scope of the consent you have provided, and require third parties to which personal information is disclosed to use the information only for the purposes for which we provide it to them.

Personal information is also collected from you if you make an employment application to us.  Such information is forwarded to the appropriate theatre location and/or HR Department, and shall be retained, used and disclosed as required to process your application.

We only collect, use and disclose personal information that is necessary for the purposes identified in this Policy, and only by legal and reasonable means. 

We do not disclose your personal information to any third party to enable it to market its products and services without first obtaining consent from you.

Protecting children’s privacy is also important to us. We request that our website visitors under the age of majority in their province of residence not disclose or provide any personal information without the consent of their parent or guardian.

Our site may contain links to other sites, including sites of affiliated companies. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of these sites. You should carefully review the privacy policies and other terms of use for such sites, and such sites may collect, use and disclose personal information in a very different manner from this site.

The security of your personal information is important to us, and we use various technical, contractual, administrative and physical security measures to protect personal information that you provide to us. We may retain your personal information as long as your relationship or transaction continues with us, and as long as reasonably necessary to address any issues and satisfy any potential legal obligations that we may have.

You should always be aware that e-mail and the internet are not secure media, and you should consider this when sending personal or confidential information to us.

If at any time you no longer wish to receive emails or other communications from us, you can discontinue such communications or any membership by following the instructions on our website.

Our website uses cookies.  This technology allows users to move more quickly through our site. Cookies are small text files that a website can use to recognize repeat users and facilitate such users' ongoing access to and use of the website. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to a user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. We do not record any of your personal information in cookies nor do we store any information about your movements on the Internet outside of our website. You can choose to decline cookies (e.g., by setting your browser to reject cookies), but if you do, some parts of our website may not operate properly. 

Since we use your personal information to provide services to you, it is important that the information be accurate and up-to-date. If during the course of your dealings with us, any of your information changes, please inform us in accordance with the contact particulars in the following paragraph so that we can amend our records.

If you have questions, comments or concerns, or wish to gain access to, or update or rectify your personal information that we may hold, please send your requests and concerns to the attention of the Privacy Officer at [empire@empiretheatres.com](mailto:empire@empiretheatres.com) or by mail to:

 Privacy Officer  
Empire Theatres Limited  
610 East River Road  
New Glasgow, NS  
B2H 3S2

Please be aware that access may not be provided to certain information which is protected by lawyer-client privilege, constitutes confidential commercial information, was collected in respect of the investigation of a breach of an agreement or of law, or is generated in respect of dispute resolution.

This Policy may be amended from time to time, and your use of this website is  
subject to other terms and conditions as posted at this website.
